{
    "misc": [
        "&cRed",
        "&4Blood Red",
        "&6Orange",
        "&eYellow",
        "&aGreen",
        "&9Blue",
        "&5Purple",
        "&dPink",
        "&fPale pink",
        "&6Yellowish brown",
        "&4Brown",
        "&2Dark Green",
        "&fColourless",
        "&fWhite",
        "&5Violet"
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What color is Fe2+",
            "answer": "&aGreen",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 31.25,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Fe3+",
            "answer": [
                "&eYellow",
                "&4Brown",
                "&6Yellowish Brown"
            ],
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 46.875,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Cu+",
            "answer": "&fColourless",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 11.71875,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Cu2+",
            "answer": "&9Blue",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 31.25,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Ni2+",
            "answer": "&aGreen",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 15.625,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Co2+",
            "answer": "&dPink",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 11.71875,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Cr2O7 2-",
            "answer": "&6Orange",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 3.90625,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Cr3+",
            "answer": "&aGreen",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 31.25,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is CrO4 2-",
            "answer": "&eYellow",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 23.4375,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is MnO4 -",
            "answer": "&5Purple",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 88.9892578125,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Mn2+",
            "answer": [
                "&fColourless",
                "&fPale pink"
            ],
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 35.15625,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is MnO",
            "answer": "&2Dark Green",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 35.15625,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is V2+",
            "answer": "&5Violet",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite"
            ],
            "weight": 15.625,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is V3+",
            "answer": "&aGreen",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 70.3125,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is V4+",
            "answer": "&9Blue",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 31.25,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Fe4+",
            "answer": "&5Violet",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite"
            ],
            "weight": 46.875,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Fe(SCN)2+",
            "answer": [
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&4Dark Red"
            ],
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet",
                "&1Deep Blue"
            ],
            "weight": 93.75,
            "time_limit": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What color is Cu(NH3)4 2+",
            "answer": "&1Deep Blue",
            "other_options": [
                "&cRed",
                "&4Blood Red",
                "&6Orange",
                "&eYellow",
                "&aGreen",
                "&9Blue",
                "&5Purple",
                "&dPink",
                "&fPale pink",
                "&6Yellowish brown",
                "&4Brown",
                "&2Dark Green",
                "&fColourless",
                "&fWhite",
                "&5Violet"
            ],
            "weight": 26.3671875,
            "time_limit": 15
        }
    ]
}